So, in this section, you learned about a
Ento, nesta seo, voc aprendeu sobre alguns cenrios de teste
few unit testing scenarios that you see in a lot of real-world applications.
de unidade que voc v em muitos aplicativos do mundo real.
More specifically, you learned how to test methods that return
Mais especificamente, voc aprendeu a testar mtodos que retornam uma
a string or a collection, you learned how to test
string ou uma coleo, aprendeu a testar mtodos nulos, mtodos
void methods, methods that throw an exception, or raise an
que lanam uma exceo ou cria um evento, e aprende
event, and you learn that you should not test private or
que voc no deve testar mtodos privados ou protegidos, porque
protected methods, because of their implementation detail. You should
de seus detalhes de implementao. Voc deve testar somente a
only test the public API, or public interface of a
API pblica ou a interface pblica de uma classe, que
class, which includes only the public members. The next
inclui apenas os membros pblicos. A prxima seo
section is all about exercises. So you will have an opportunity
sobre exerccios. Ento voc ter a oportunidade de aplicar
to apply what you have learned in the course so far. So, I will see you in the next
o que aprendeu no curso at agora. Ento, eu vou te
section.
ver na prxima seo.